Normally I drive across the
market square. But we have to wait.
Have a nice day! Is
that the getaway car?
Getaway... A shot! Quick!
The helicopter has already
taken off. One moment please!
When do we storm it?
- In 10 minutes.
In 10 minutes the heli
lands. Don't lose your nerve!
I'll give you exactly five!
- Asshole!
Mr. Stich! Forgive me! Lessing!
I'm the new one from Hamburg.
Already? What's going on here?
A maniac wants a
million, a heli and a pizza.
A hostage is dead. Officer Dorn
is now his exchange hostage.
Who?
Kira Dorn. He wanted a woman.
The SWAT team needs 10 more minutes.
Here's the pizza!
- Thanks, Steffen!
Who's bringing it in?
Are you sure? Give me your phone!
Call me in three minutes!
* Suspenseful music *
Two minutes ago, they said the
helicopter was in the air.
And now you're bringing a pizza.
You want to storm in!
Not with a pregnant hostage!
Then we're safe for a while.
Is everything okay?
The doctor says yes.
What is it going to be?
It doesn't matter. As long as it's a healthy boy.
Can you guys shut up?
He's hungry.
* The phone rings. *
Yes. Yes.
Hold on! It's for you.
You despicable coward!
A pregnant woman!
Hans is lying. We're getting out.
Was that a drill?
What did you think?
Oh! Excuse me!
Lessing.
Hans Bangen. Not that bad.
I didn't know about you.
Me neither.
Extra cheese! That's awesome!
Yummy! Stop eating that crap all the time!
So yummy!
Are you keeping up?
A slice of pizza, Lessing?
You should have briefed me!
One in three officers didn't
know that it was a drill.
Realistic. Is that
different in Hamburg?
I know what realistic looks like!
I wouldn't send a pregnant woman.
Who knows? Why does
she work in the field?
She works until the contractions start.
She doesn't let anyone hold her back.
This has to stay between us.
He had mental health
problems in Hamburg. Burnout.
KDD. Brutal job. Very
few stick with it for long.
Handle him with care!
We'll get him back on his feet.
Colleagues! All in all,
it was pretty decent.
Cordon: flawless. Communication
with the citizen: good.
But, Steffen, the pizza from
Mykonos was an unnecessary risk.
Next time: Mario! Thank you!
If that's going too fast for you,
no problem. Just get here first!
No! We're looking for a gang that
steals toilet paper from the town hall.
And someone who smears
cars with ground meat.
It was human ground meat!
Mrs. Dorn! Can you come down?
What's going on?
He was standing in the Poseck garden.
Since last night. Come take a look!
That looks like blood.
Who is it registered to?
Brigitte Hoppe, handbag in front.
Hans, come down and bring
the blacklight lamp with you!
Brigitte Hoppe is the Sausage
Queen. Butcher shop with six branches.
They make the best
Thuringian, Fat Hoppe.
She's not that fat at all. That's
what the sausage is called.
Ah, I see.
That was quite a scratch.
That is definitely
blood. How much?
It needs to be extracted
first. But there's a lot.
A female butcher deals with blood.
Could she be the ground meat perpetrator?
She doesn't leave a handbag
behind. How tall is she?
1.63 meters. For that,
the seat is too far back.
Sigmar Hoppe is the
son and junior director.
I bet, other than the mother, no woman
has ever been in the house. Sausage!
Lessing. Dorn. Criminal
Police. Can we come in?
Yes.
That's great! Where is that?
In Heilbad Heiligenstadt.
Did you do this?
Do you think that's too far-fetched?
Good morning! Hello!
Mrs. Reuter! Then let
me get you out quickly.
Yes.
I doubt your
little-sausage theory.
Is your mother at home?
Hold on!
Mom! Oh! She's
probably already at work.
No. And her cell phone is off too.
When did you last see your mother?
Last evening at the
office. Can I help you?
It's possible that something
happened to your mother.
We found her car at Poseck's
Garden. Her handbag was inside.
Strange!
There's blood in the trunk.
Mom!
She's a hunter. I don't know
what she's been driving around for.
There was also an
axe in the car. This size.
Mother always
butchers the pigs herself.
Can we head upstairs?
Yes.
Don't touch anything! She notices
everything and then she'll kill me.
Meat-nose?
Yeah, from the cold storage. Unpleasant.
Did your mother have any plans yesterday?
Not that I know of.
She often has appointments off-site, but was
looking forward to watching "Tatort" on Sunday.
Then she must have been at home.
Probably. I went to bed early.
* A football match is being broadcast loudly
on the TV. *
You would have noticed that.
Sorry!
We need something for
the DNA comparison.
With the blood in the trunk.
Exactly.
It's working again. Are we done?
Everything will come to light.
Are you also driving
your mother's car?
No. I don't understand the question.
We're worried about
your mother. Aren't you?
Blood, hatchet, handbag!
This doesn't seem to worry you.
Thank God! There she is!
Mom, something's going on here.
Who's there? I can barely
understand you. Please speak louder!
Where? How much? In two hours? What?
Hello!
Hello! My mother has been kidnapped. I
am supposed to pay a ransom. No police!
Was that a man or a woman?
Don't know. The voice was distorted.
Do you have any idea
who it might have been?
No. She gets along with
everyone. That's nonsense.
Her husband pulled the strings
and she handled the money.
The Hoppes own real estate. She
canceled her contract with a daycare.
She doesn't help the Weimar Food Bank
either, because it's not tax-deductible.
And the butcher shops
are still running fine?
You haven't tried a
fat Hoppe yet!
You know your mother's
reputation. No, I don't!
Instead of a heart ...
she has just a purse?
And many enemies. Do
you absolutely have no idea?
The money must be at
Theater Square in 2 hours.
That's too much for you. Your
father died last week. Our condolences.
Yes.
Is the kidnapping related to that?
It's all happening in very quick succession.
Kidnappings end all the
better, the higher the ransom is.
How much was demanded?
45,000 euros.
That's a lot of money
for many people.
We'll take care of everything.
Who's playing the couple? Mandy, Rocco,
can you bring yourselves to go through with it?
Is that right? Exchange,
Theaterplatz, in the trash can?
In two hours. Nadine
Reuter was at Sigmar Hoppe's.
On her scooter. She stayed over at his
place; in front of us they used the formal "you."
Lecko mio!
Can we go to the theater?
I'm up next!
What about Ms. Reuter,
besides what's obvious?
She buried two husbands.
We couldn't prove anything.
She thought they were rich. Wrong!
What's obvious about her?
How many undercover officers?
At least ten!
What about the blood analysis?
And are there fingerprints on the axe?
No, none.
Check the scratches on the bumper!
What a shame it's so busy right now.
It's Monday, after all.
That's your office.
Talk to the residents again!
Maybe someone saw something.
And the guy from the
tow service! Thanks, bye!
Nothing at Poseck's Garden. No
one saw anything, no blood traces.
The car was parked there. And
Mrs. Hoppe was dropped off.
No. No person fits in the
trunk. Not in one piece.
Max, do you still have the city runabout?
Yes, why?
It's too tight.
What?
Oh, I see. Should we?
It's too tight.
Try angling it more to the side!
Yes.
I told you so.
Head back!
Almost there.
Ouch!
Aha! Great!
* Lessing is knocking from inside. *
I can't open the trunk.
Do you have a cutting torch?
The blood belongs to Ms. Hoppe.
The blood is Ms. Hoppe's.
It's 1.5 liters.
She was injured outside
the trunk. That means: even more blood.
Then she barely survived.
That means: the perpetrator is demanding
ransom for a corpse?
* Suspenseful music *
The coachman again!
Caspar Bogdanski. He's harmless.
His daughter is my brother's
ex. She turned on the desk lamp.
Sigmar Hoppe can hit the road.
Understood.
Yeah, go ahead and wave us off!
The bachelors are great.
The bachelors aren't ours.
The couple is doing
great. They're really in love.
Stich can't find out. He doesn't
like romance in the workplace.
Who is the father of your child?
Is he a cop too?
He's an astrophysicist and
still lives in Berlin.
Master or journeyman?
He discovered a three-armed barred
spiral galaxy. It bears my name.
(he sings) A barred spiral galaxy
that bears your name!
Hello! Who do we have here?
That's Olm, the head of the
Trade Registry. Forget about it!
That's obviously fake. No one
could possibly be that stupid.
My water is breaking.
What's her pay grade?
Come on, come on, come on! Over here!
Cyclists one and two, take over!
All clear! I've got it.
* Suspenseful music *
Everyone waits.
Go!
Left onto Wielandstraße! Quickly!
How did you do that?
Elevator, Lessing.
Follow Olm! Keep your distance!
Watch the trash cans until we're sure
we have the suspect.
What do you want with Olm?
Did she rob a bank?
Does the woman have a first name?
Olm?
* Suspenseful music *
Brrr!
Well, bravo! That's coming off.
This will make us famous. The money
transfer from Weimar - failed!
What kind of money transfer?
* Suspenseful music *
Your wife gets a parking
sticker for the city and we'll forget about it.
Hand over your driver's
license and we'll forget everything!
Or should two colleagues
pick up your driver's license?
Windmühlenstraße
14. Is that still current?
You'll hear from me.
Good day! Lessing.
Olm.
Did you forget anything?
Why?
In your handbag.
Oh, the envelope!
It should go to the lost and found. So much money!
Who throws stuff like that away?
Do you have any gum?
Are you crazy? I'm supposed to have
kidnapped Hoppe?
You didn't know anything about the ransom?
Ransom for a corpse?
Mrs. Hoppe is dead?
Do you want to tell us that?
Is it a hidden camera?
She didn't want to go to the lost-and-found.
Yes! Be glad that
my chewing gum ...
Too stupid to throw away chewing gum?
What audacity!
What flavor is this?
Dead Smurf?
Watch out! In 20 minutes I have
an appointment with the mayor.
Should I tell him that you both
are accusing me of murder?
* Loud Laughter *
The call to Sigmar Hoppe was
at 9.47. Where were you then?
In a meeting for the campaign
"Weimar shimmers". The witness is Stich.
I understand.
You may go. You'll hear from me.
Is the Trade Office also
responsible for hygiene at butchers?
Yes, and?
Did you have anything to do with Mrs. Hoppe?
No. Our contact was the son.
Things will be different now.
Why?
He'll probably sell.
Why sell?
He didn't feel like it anymore. Is that it?
The matter is settled. Wasn't
anyone at the trash can?
Deposit-bottle Kalli was there
and a ball landed on Marius.
What's the status of things?
We had to let her go.
The kidnapper could still come.
No. He must have seen how
the envelope was taken out.
He'll definitely reach out again.
Mr. Hoppe! What do you
have to do with Nadine Reuter?
Nadine Reuter gives
city tours for tourists.
I offered her a catering concept.
And I have a bloated stomach.
Mr. Hoppe! She stayed
overnight at your place.
She leaves the house and right
after that the alleged kidnapper calls.
What do you mean by that?
Mrs. Reuter doesn't want a butcher.
She wants to shop. Not in
Weimar, but in Paris and New York.
Watch your tone!
Do you want to sell the company?
For that to happen, it would
first have to be mine. Better?
Yes.
Thank you!
Mrs. Dorn! We have to look
for Mrs. Hoppe or her body.
A full squad?
That would draw too much attention.
The perpetrator still knows
nothing about us, unless ...
Sigmar Hoppe is the perpetrator.
Is this too much for your condition?
No!
Is there a father to the
child who supports you?
Mr. Stich! Boundaries!
Private, professional.
Boundaries! Very good!
Hans!
Can you cross-reference that with
the traces from Brigitte Hoppe's car?
Whose is that? Sigmar's.
There were dandruff flakes from
him on the driver's seat. Nothing else.
You didn't have a negative.
The mtDNA is identical to
Mrs. Hoppe, but Y chromosome.
So that can only be...?
That's biology. Right?
The son!
Exactly!
Ha! So he did drive
the car after all!
Bogdanski!
Dad, you haven't eaten anything yet.
- I'll treat you to a big meal later!
I reserved a table
by the window.
What's going on? Do you want
to apologize for something again?
I drove Kira and a colleague.
Something's up with the Hoppe case.
It's quite possible that
it won't come to trial.
But water damage is water damage.
No matter what happened to Hoppe.
We need to go to Sigmar Hoppe.
What? Why?
He was driving the car, after
all. That could have been earlier.
He'd be the right height.
That one too! We'll deal with him.
Let him fend for himself.
His city tours used to be the
most exciting ones in Weimar.
Why exciting?
He knows a story about every wall.
Does he also know about Anna
Amalia's and Goethe's affair?
Lessing! Straight-A Abitur? Okay.
Bogdanski lives in a house
that belongs to Hoppe.
There was water damage and
Hoppe is suing for damages.
The hearing was supposed to be
next week. It's about 35,000 euros.
He has been driving around empty the whole time.
He's looking for passengers.
There were some here.
But: empty!
His wife died two years ago.
Things have been going downhill for him ever since.
He has nothing to lose.
See? That's what I mean.
We're heading to Goethe's Garden House.
That's where he wrote "Iphigenia on Tauris”，
"Egmont" and the famous
"Evening Song of the Hunter".
It's called "Hunter's Evening Song".
- I have to go. We'll talk tonight.
"Still and wild I creep through the field,
cocking my gun barrel."
"Your beloved's image hovers ..."
- Mr. Bogdanski!
Between twelve and one, you were
driving around empty on Theater Square.
And when customers finally
came in, you turned them down.
They were drunk. Is there
anything special to see here?
No. What?
It looks like you were
interested in the trash can.
I don't understand. What
was I supposed to do?
Brigitte Hoppe was kidnapped
and the ransom was in the trash can.
Oh! And now you
think that it was me.
They're going through a really hard time
right now. And the trouble with Mrs. Hoppe.
35,000 euros! You
can't possibly afford that.
No money for a lawyer. So
I'm hardly kidnapping anyone.
Mrs. Dorn told me
what a fine man you are.
The situation is difficult
and you're not a bad person.
87.9 percent of crimes are
not committed by monsters.
But by perfectly nice people
who are simply desperate.
You don't even know me.
You drove to Hoppe's to
give her a piece of your mind.
And then things went
completely out of hand.
You didn't mean to hurt
her, but you'd been drinking.
Now both of you, stop it!
Suddenly she was dead and
you were completely thrown.
That's why you wanted
to blackmail Sigmar Hoppe.
You have every right to, given
how terrible his mother was to you.
Hold on! Now I'm supposed
to have killed her as well.
Watch what you say, girl!
Mr. Bogdanski!
Did you load the body into
your car and dump it somewhere?
How would you even do that?
Is it too heavy for you?
I don't have a driver's license
Our car belongs to Lotte.
You'd better talk to Sigmar Hoppe!
He raced past me yesterday on the way
to the slaughterhouse. It was around eight.
I thought he was heading over to the horses.
See? That's what I mean.
That was actually meant for the
camper. But it's needed here now.
The Olm, the Driver, Sigmar Hoppe!
The Olm had the
money, but no motive.
Bogdanski has a motive,
but no driver's license.
Only Sigmar is a mystery.
Everyone knows his mother thinks
he's good for nothing. Poor little sausage!
Then let's take a look around here.
Why should I come here?
Where can we talk in peace?
Please, come in!
Give me the fat Berta!
Is that a sausage, too?
Sorry! I'm not having
my sensitive day today.
Is this video-monitored?
Yes, because of the hygiene regulations.
Can we take a look?
Yes.
That's Mrs. Hoppe!
Can we fast-forward?
Yes, with the arrow.
Here?
Yes.
Who do we have here?
Apparently, nothing special.
A quiet Sunday evening?
What was in the bag you threw away?
Meat scraps.
Does your mother often follow
you around with a big shopping bag?
No.
What did your mother's letter say?
I need to think about that.
Yes.
He probably doesn't remember what
the argument was about either.
No.
Where do the waste materials go?
Can you show us the room?
There are lots of
containers and a downpipe.
The waste is here. Through the
pipe, everything falls down.
It smells awful. Not a
Hamburg fish market.
Which container is from yesterday?
I can't tell you that.
Now is a good moment for
your first Jungle Test.
I was already in the car.
Please!
This is really good stuff
for the Hoppe Special!
I could already eat another one!
Mrs. Dorn, please!
* Suspenseful music *
That's an envelope!
For Brigitte in case of my death.
Her father has been dead for a week.
Why did she only open the letter
yesterday? At work? On Sunday?
She probably only found it
yesterday.
I have a feeling about what it said. Mother
searched the whole house after that.
What specifically?
The spice mix of the fat Hoppe.
Only Father knew it
from his father.
The end of the fat Hoppe! The
company is worthless without the recipe.
Here!
That's a whole fortune. Are you
just going to throw that in the trash?
Maybe it's not his.
But his mother's!
Hans, send a big
team to Hoppe's company!
We need DNA samples and
the operation must be stopped.
Sigmar Hoppe! His own mother!
We only have circumstantial
evidence. He refuses to testify.
No body, no case. That's why
he won't confess to murder.
Exactly 100,000 euros! With
finger-prints of an old acquaintance!
Interrogation, both of you!
Sigmar!
What did you do?
Actress!
Strange! That guy with the woman!
Do you find her attractive?
Of course not.
But she radiates a
certain approachability.
That could surely
morally renew some man.
Not me!
I bet you were
in school with her.
Well. Everything was
actually going great.
Junior boss, big
car, limitless cash.
There was only one problem: Mother.
Why did Mrs. Reuter have the money?
Mother wanted Nadine to leave.
Was that worth 100,000 to her?
Yes.
Why didn't you say that earlier?
You're not from here.
No.
When it comes to Nadine,
everyone thinks of greed and murder.
You've already passed
judgment on me anyway.
Wrong! But any other woman would
have left after the second dead ex.
And you swagger around
with your proud breasts.
You need some backbone for
that. Forgive me! My frivolous day!
By the way, congratulations!
Finally no longer a virgin!
The 100,000 were certainly tempting.
But you wanted everything once again.
Nadine gave you the money. And then?
She didn't want to live with me like that.
As long as your mother is alive!
You crashed at his place
yesterday. He called me.
He was arguing with his
mother and needed me.
For what? To dispose of the body?
And with his mother's phone
you staged a kidnapping.
Then I say the kidnapper wants
45.000. Do you take me for a fool?
A genius! You know about
the lawsuit with the coach driver.
It's about a similar amount and it
was clear that we'd come across it.
You're giving me too much credit.
You said you never
drive your mother's car.
How did your dandruff
end up on the headrest?
Because ...
I was refueling last week.
How sweet!
You're not a butcher. Your photos
show what you were never allowed to have.
Because of Mother. How long have
you wanted out of the company?
It was agreed that I would study
photography after my butchery apprenticeship.
After Father died, I told
Mother that it was time to quit.
But for your mother, Mrs.
Reuter was the real reason.
Yes.
That's why Mother had
to go. At whatever cost.
When she came with the hatchet,
you thought of a permanent solution.
I drove away after that. I
know nothing about a hatchet.
I haven't seen Mother again
since then. You have to believe me.
Did she drive over to you after the fight?
You took her son away from her.
She storms in and you
can get rid of her for good.
You tell Sigmar,
what happened.
You dispose of the body and
spend the night together.
But she doesn't even
know where I live.
Such a good match! And now it's all
gone up in smoke. Just like back then!
Slept with the German teacher and
got held back because of French.
I didn't do anything to you. I never took any of
your friends away from you at school.
You simply didn't have any.
Ms. Dorn, come here!
No body, no prosecutor!
They'll crack eventually!
We need to let her go. I
had a shit school life, too!
* Melancholic music *
Nadine!
Please don't leave me alone!
No! That's insane!
Can I help you?
What do you have in mind now?
I don't know yet.
I'm not as smart as Kira.
I have to use what I have.
But I always chose
the wrong men.
Maybe you'll give me a call sometime.
Okay!
Oh, I see. And when is he coming back?
Okay, thanks!
I also printed something for us.
My rock bottom
was in 10th grade.
Acne. Uncontrollable erections.
Because of my
nearsightedness, no P.E. class.
Nadine dumped
Hoppe. I just saw that.
Are you falling for it?
That's a tactic!
But if he ends up in prison,
his inheritance is gone.
Yes, Ms. Reuter! Lessing here!
Right, the one from just now.
I completely forgot to
apologize for Colleague Dorn.
That was really ... Yeah,
she is quite a bitch.
Absolutely, yes! No idea
who got her pregnant.
Yeah. Oh! I think she's coming.
The floor is shaking.
Yeah. Maybe we can continue
discussing this over dinner.
At your place? Yeah. Today? Sure!
At eight. That works!
Oh! A moment! Just a second!
Ms. Dorn, cake again?
Okay. So see you this evening!
Okay. Yes, see you then!
Okay. Ciao!
We need to make her an offer.
Then she'll hand over Sigmar.
How do you have her number?
She gave it to me.
You'll be wired. If Nadine testifies
against Sigmar, that's going to happen.
What's this?
Matching the car scratches
against the paint file.
The Hoppe clipped a Porsche
928. It belongs to a music professor.
I called the university. He's been
on an Asian tour for three weeks.
The address! Did you see the address?
No.
Windmühlenstraße 16!
Is it Windmühlenstraße 14?
- You'll hear from me!
Mrs. "You-Heard-About-Me"
lives next door.
Can't you smell it?
It's getting worse.
What is it?
Furry, rotten, sweetish.
With traces of a corpse.
Were you ever a sommelier?
I thought pregnant women smelled good.
Does that have anything to do with me?
You smell wonderful.
Mrs. Olm lives just
around the corner.
Mrs. Hoppe was at
your place yesterday.
She was so angry that when
she parked, she scraped a car.
I haven't seen Mrs. Hoppe. I
want to speak to your boss.
He sends his regards.
Warm regards!
What's interesting is that the trade
office issues the bratwurst stand licenses.
They're put out to
tender. Oh, excuse me!
I've also had a table burn
through. Those are unscrupulous fellows.
The Hoppes have the
best locations here.
Goethe House, Schiller Museum,
Castle, Theater Square.
I let myself be bribed.
There's just one catch.
I handed the tenders over
to my deputy.
Don't arrest him! Otherwise
I'll be in hot water again!
Mrs. Dorn, you know
this place better than I do.
Are there any other suspects?
Simply everyone hated Hoppe.
* Phone rings. *
Dorn. Lotte! What is it?
You interrogated Papa for an hour.
Are you nuts?
He was behaving strangely.
Of course, he's always plastered!
Poor thing! And you're still beating on him!
We're just doing our job.
He talks a lot of nonsense!
But that he kills someone ...
Are you still on?
I have to hang up.
Okay.
What? Nothing.
Let's go, time to wire it up!
Test!
Okay.
Your teacher disappeared without a
trace. He must have gone to the West.
Six years after the fall of the Wall!
How old should I be?
* Lessing rings the doorbell. *
Now I suppose I'll have to cancel the table
by the window.
Hey!
- I dozed off, just for a moment.
Yesterday on my way home.
I thought she ran into the carriage.
- Why didn't you call the police?
They would have definitely made me blow
into the breathalyzer. That would be our end!
Then you call Hoppe
and demand a ransom?
It is the just punishment for
suing us.
There are no coincidences in the universe.
Uncontrollable forces are at work!
There's always a Big Bang in your little corner.
These forces wanted Hoppe to
actually do something good in the end.
How much did you ask for?
- 45,000!
That little? Are you an idiot?
No wonder Kira suspected you.
That was a bit low.
- Yes.
Maybe my plan wasn't
as elaborate as I thought.
What do we do now?
(Nadine) I hope you like
mushrooms. It depends where.
In the living room.
You can't talk to Kira.
No, that's true.
She's losing it over me.
It's spelled "meinetwegen"!
Yes. She's a bitch.
What a crazy bitch!
A very crazy bitch.
One thing up front: My two men
died a completely normal death.
They were old and glad to
have a few good days with me.
You have no luck with men.
Sigmar Hoppe gets you involved
in a kidnapping and a murder.
How did he talk you into it?
That's not how it is at all.
Then how?
He's the first one who truly loves me.
With him, I don't feel stupid.
And he knows a lot and
still he listens to me.
And it couldn't have been him.
Why not?
When I arrived, his mother was there.
She apologized and drove off.
Yes, in the trunk!
Damn!
I hate it when that happens.
That's the job.
I find that uncomfortable.
Sigmar said he last saw his mother
at the butcher's.
You don't have to lie to me, Mrs.
Reuter. You know it was him.
Now you feel like
it's all your fault.
Do you find it romantic that
someone killed his mother for you?
* She sobs. *
One, two, action!
Whoa! That guy really went
and shattered the nose to bits.
Was it me, Lotte?
Or had it already been done?
It could have been Sigmar.
- Why Sigmar?
I could understand him. As a
kid, his mom always left him alone.
As an adult, he was her little sausage.
A customer of Lischka's saw
him being led away in handcuffs.
He was released for lack of evidence.
- Then we'll provide the evidence.
We film Sigmar while he
buries the body.
Dad, the body is here!
- Not yet, Lotte! Not yet!
Plan B.
Thank you! It was Kira's idea after all
that you call me.
Because she hates me!
Why exactly?
I have a photo from 11th grade.
Oh God!
Here it is. You don't even
look at it.
I know what Ms. Dorn looked
like. Fantastic!
Okay! Now I have to go.
Give me the photo back!
* A door is closed. *
I didn't look at it.
May I?
Fancy a surprise visit?
Have you found Mother?
No. We're looking for traces, in case
you killed her here.
Why should I let you in?
84 percent of people who
refuse, are the perpetrators.
Feel free to look around!
* Suspenseful music *
Is anyone sitting there?
Absolutely not!
Mommy!
She probably
always liked to sit here.
Is she dead?
Yes, she is dead.
Then call a doctor!
Yes, we will. Now let's take
a look at your freezer first.
I'll notify Stich and
forensics. Okay. Here! Come!
Well? Do you believe me now?
Who would benefit from
the body being found here?
Maybe he saw you kill your
mother. A freeloader
I didn't kill my mother!
Possibly. But what if you did?
Then you would have gotten
rid of the body quickly.
This is all a nightmare.
I still want to see the basement.
"The gate gazes shut
and God and Heaven pound."
Not "knock"!
You are to stay by the body.
It's not going anywhere.
Lessing!
No, it's Stramm. August Stramm.
Plan B was garbage!
* A police siren wails. *
None of the neighbors saw anything.
But I did!
Okay! I'm coming!
So? Where is the body?
Gone. We found a sugar cube.
Then she drives
through the city. Pardon?
The body in the
back seat. Bogdanski!
Well then!
Mr. Hoppe, my condolences.
Mrs. Dorn spoke of free-
riders. What did she mean?
Someone had hoped that you
would make the body disappear.
And then?
They could have extorted you.
The extortioner kidnapped the body.
Apparently!
You stay here!
Yes.
Can we take a look in your
trunk, Lotte?
Now?
Let's get it over with!
* Suspenseful music *
Dry.
Wow!
I still have my lamp, too.
It's on the desk.
Kira! I almost belonged to your
family. Is that enough now?
Carlos has rheumatism.
Ice is good for that.
Your father would be turning in his
grave if he saw you here.
My father is still alive.
I said "would" too.
Hold on!
There ... There's a hose that's leaking.
* Thrilling music *
There's a hose leaking here.
We'll come back tomorrow with a
search warrant.
The KT will find something, even if it's
just a hair from the Hoppe.
Good night!
I can't take it anymore!
Oh my! Hans lives here. He goes for a walk around
that time with his farty mastiff.
Then Stich fires me after my maternity
leave. Romance in the workplace!
I thought we'd be alone
here. Welcome to Weimar!
We could switch to the informal "you"
now. Everyone here uses the informal "you."
Exactly! Yes.
You're fine with the formal "you."
I almost figured that.
If this hostage-taker had done
something to you and our son ...
I would have
killed him without hesitation.
There!
One, two!
Good that you're here! I just
confessed everything to Lotte.
She didn't know anything. She said,
we have to call the police.
I did that too.
But the line was busy.
Mrs. Olm wants to take
my chauffeur's license away.
The licenses are limited.
She's cashing in on it.
Dad is her victim.
- Because I supposedly have a drinking problem.
Everyone drinks when they're upset.
- Or when it's cold!
Or on a Monday.
Or when a body needs to be gotten rid of.
Did you kill Mrs. Hoppe?
No. He ran over her in his sleep.
* Crash *
Up at Lindenberg. Sunday night.
He woke up, but the Hoppe
was already dead before.
And in a flash he hatched a plan.
He wants ransom for the corpse.
Then he noticed us and wanted
to kill two birds with one stone.
45.000 in the trash can at the theater
for a lifetime coachman's license.
That was no coincidence.
The Olm was supposed
to reach into the trash can.
Not bad! Olm should have paid
45,000 to renew her license.
Olm should be locked up,
so you can have your peace.
Attempted bribery, extortion.
What did he do to Ms. Hoppe?
Disturbing the dead, concealment.
Withholding evidence,
obstruction of justice.
Papa!
Respect!
What do we do with Olm now?
She'll be hearing from us.
How's it looking?
Severe occipital wound.
She bled for a
long time.
But it doesn't necessarily
have to have been fatal.
But that should have been
enough: strangulation marks.
What was the weapon here?
I might know after the
autopsy. So, tomorrow.
You mean in two hours.
Are you the new guy from Hamburg?
Yes. Lessing.
Can I just ...
Hooray, the letter!
Frozen, thawed, frozen, thawed!
The death of the fat Hoppe!
What if this isn't the
sausage recipe at all?
Then the letter was the reason
why she took the fat Berta.
It leads us to the
murderer. If we can read it.
I know who can reconstruct it:
the one at the "Anna Amalia!"
Heads up!
Stefan, it's Kira! Do you have
anything going on tonight?
Stone cold. I have a letter
here with water damage.
How fast can you get it done?
You're the best. I'll send it over.
Bye!
See you tomorrow too. Wow!
We need to call the boss.
I've already done that.
Sigmar Hoppe is taken into custody overnight.
The coachman too.
And secures the forest path to
Lindenberg until the K9 unit arrives!
* The cat hisses. *
Sigmar!
I can't sleep. I keep
thinking about how it was for me.
People thought I had killed two people.
But there is the presumption of innocence.
Everyone is considered innocent until
legal proof of guilt is established.
That also applies to the press.
I love you too.
Good morning!
Chic!
Thank you! Weimar shimmers!
All department heads are taking part.
Stich is also in the photo.
Let's hurry! I was already done
with Mrs. Hoppe at seven.
That was in the wound.
A nice dick! Maybe a
piece of a glass vase.
And something else.
Here!
This could be gold.
And the glass shard
the edge of a tabletop?
Possible.
This isn't gold. It's
brass, Lessing!
Bye!
Whoa! So, I can smell it too now.
Man!
The marten clearly
hit a car.
A suicide.
Crash through the window!
* Police siren sounds. *
* Police siren *
Oh! I think the marten has gotten through.
We're pursuing a black station wagon,
Wagner Lane!
Pardon! Excuse me!
Pardon!
* Suspenseful music *
Excuse me! Pardon!
Weapon down!
This will never work between us!
What?
I won't marry a wimp.
Marry?
If it's to be, then it's to be done right!
With all the trimmings: horse, carriage, dress!
Crown.
She's always dreamed of that.
Me too.
He's a true romantic.
I will shoot for real.
You're not making me a widow.
You won't shoot.
82 percent of such cases
end without bloodshed.
Nonsense! You haven't
read a single statistic yet.
I get through in 99 percent of
cases. The Hoppe ruined my life.
All good!
She rang the bell, I opened the
door and she came at me with an axe.
She slammed into the
table. It was self-defense.
Blood everywhere. She had
bled like a pig.
That's why you didn't call the police.
The bitch had to be gotten rid of.
You shoved her into
the trunk.
Later, you saw that
the bitch was still alive.
Then you strangled her.
Yes.
But that's not self-defense. Right?
So what is it? Why then?
I have the letter.
She confessed.
"Brigitte! If you're
reading this, I'm dead."
"I can't tell you the
recipe for the fat bitch."
"You know I only ever loved
one woman. It wasn't you."
"Sigmar doesn't want the
company and you don't deserve it."
"I leave the recipe to
my beloved Karin. Fuck it!"
Karin?
That's no big deal. Karin Olm!
They have the recipe
for the Fat Hoppe.
The recipe is at home in the envelope.
On the outside it said:
"Dear Karin!"
"No fire, no coal,
can burn so hot ..."
"Like a secret, quiet love, of
which no one knows a thing."
* Romantic piano music *
Boss!
We have something to tell you.
I already know.
Make two more! The Fat-Hoppe
recipe was in the Olms' apartment.
Sigmar is selling the company, but
the sausage will still be produced.
Good work, colleagues!
Thanks!
We can also reveal the recipe
for the Fat Dorn.
Mr. Lessing!
Boundaries! Professional,
Personal! Boundaries!
Subtitle:
Line 21 / Frank H. Richter